http://www.editing.co.uk/index.php/cookie-privacy-policy.html

HomeOfflineOnline & File delivery (DPP)Colour GradingProductionContactShowreels
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how  Jim Allison Engineering Limited T/A JAe  uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.
JAe is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
JAe may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 2019
How we collect and use your information:
This privacy policy tells you what to expect when using services provided by JAe and the editing.co.uk web site and details how we use cookies to maintain services for visitors and users of our website.
Collecting Visitors Information
We collect information in a way which does not identify anyone unless this information is provided by you to us by other communications such as email, text or phone. When someone visits our web site we may collect standard Internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site, how long visitors stayed on pages and how the site was found. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of individuals visiting our website. We will not associate any data gathered from this log information with any personally identifying information from any other source.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
• Name and job title.
• Contact information including phone or mobile number and address.
• Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests related to business.
• Other information relevant to customer work engagement.
• Your internet protocol address and details of your browsing activity during visits to our website
• Records of correspondence with you whether by telephone, email, social media or otherwise.
• Social media profile information, including profile name and picture.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
• Comply with any applicable law, legal process or enforcement by any  regulatory  body which is binding on JAe;
• Detect and protect against fraud or other security issues.
• We may use the information to improve our products and services.
People Telephoning
When you call our telephone lines (land or mobile) we collect Calling Line Identification (CLI) information. We can use this information to help improve operational efficiency and allow us to call you back.
Disclosure of Personal Information
In most circumstances we will not disclose personal data without consent. Where we need to disclose personal information to conduct our services and business operations and fulfil contractual obligations  we will only share personal details that are relevant and necessary to conduct such operations. If we need to use your personal information for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. If, at any point security is breached we will inform you of this.
We will never sell or disclose any information gathered from any source to individuals or third parties. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information and include:
• Site access and IT access controls – only authorised personnel are able to gain access to premises, buildings and rooms where your information is stored electronically within our IT systems.
• Controls – only authorised personnel are able to gain access to IT security controls – use of appropriate technology and security measures to ensure secure storage of your information.
• Policies & procedures – comprehensive data protection and IT security policies and procedures setting out the way in which your information must be handled.
• Training – delivery of ongoing data protection and IT security training to all staff handling your information.
Use of Cookies
When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable.
This site does not use Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We may  use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
• If whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
• If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at head office address or emailing us at
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
• you can request that we remove or delete your personal information
• Personal data are not kept longer than is necessary for their purpose. Paper record are incinerated, digital records are securely destroyed and emails securely archived.
• We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection  Act 1998. A small fee may be payable if your request is unfounded or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with the request in such circumstances. Please note that we may need to request information from you to confirm your identity and establish your entitlement to these rights. If you are not satisfied with our processing of your personal information, you also have the right to make a complaint to the relevant supervisory authority
If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the registered office address. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
JAe’s Terms and Conditions and Privacy/GDPR Policy are available on request.
Jim Allison Engineering Limited T/A JAe Ltd
Registered in Scotland No: SC 194128 Vat Reg No: 151 4329 34
Registered Office & Accounts: 5 Abbots Moss Drive, Falkirk, FK1 5UA Tel/Fax: 01324 625 052
This privacy policy sets out how  Jim Allison Engineering Limited T/A JAe  uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.
JAe is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
JAe may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 2018
How we collect and use your information:
This privacy policy tells you what to expect when using services provided by the editing.co.uk web site and details how we use cookies to maintain services for visitors and users of our website.
Collecting Visitors Information
We collect information in a way which does not identify anyone unless this information is provided by you to us by other communications such as email, text or phone. When someone visits our web site we may collect standard Internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site, how long visitors stayed on pages and how the site was found. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of individuals visiting our website. We will not associate any data gathered from this log information with any personally identifying information from any other source.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
• name and job title
• contact information including phone or mobile number and address
• demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
• other information relevant to customer work engagement
• Your internet protocol address and details of your browsing activity during visits to our website
• Records of correspondence with you whether by telephone, email, social media or otherwise.
• Social media profile information, including profile name and picture.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
• Comply with any applicable law, legal process or enforcement by any  regulatory
body which is binding on JAe;
• Detect and protect against fraud or other security issues.
• We may use the information to improve our products and services.
People Telephoning
When you call our telephone lines (land or mobile) we collect Calling Line Identification (CLI) information. We can use this information to help improve operational efficiency and allow us to call you back.
Disclosure of Personal Information
In most circumstances we will not disclose personal data without consent. Where we need to disclose personal information to conduct our services and business operations and fulfil contractual obligations  we will only share personal details that are relevant and necessary to conduct such operations. If we need to use your personal information for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. If, at any point security is breached we will inform you of this.
We will never sell or disclose any information gathered from any source to individuals or third parties. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information and include:
• Site access and IT access controls – only authorised personnel are able to gain access to premises, buildings and rooms where your information is stored electronically within our IT systems.
• controls – only authorised personnel are able to gain access to IT security controls – use of appropriate technology and security measures to ensure secure storage of your information.
• Policies & procedures – comprehensive data protection and IT security policies and procedures setting out the way in which your information must be handled.
• Training – delivery of ongoing data protection and IT security training to all staff handling your information.
Use of Cookies
When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable.
This site uses Cookies
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We may  use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
• whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
• if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at head office address or emailing us at
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
• you can request that we remove or delete your personal information
• We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection  Act 1998. A small fee may be payable if your request is unfounded or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with the request in such circumstances. Please note that we may need to request information from you to confirm your identity and establish your entitlement to these rights. If you are not satisfied with our processing of your personal information, you also have the right to make a complaint to the relevant supervisory authority
If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the registered office address. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
JAe’s Terms and Conditions are available on request.
Jim Allison Engineering Limited T/A JAe Ltd
Registered in Scotland No: SC 194128 Vat Reg No: 151 4329 34
Registered Office & Accounts: 5 Abbots Moss Drive, Falkirk, FK1 5UA Tel/Fax: 01324 625 052
Cookie & Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2012. All Rights Reserved.
